(synth strings and pop beat)
♪ Baby, can't you see I'm calling ♪
♪ A guy like you should wear a warning ♪
♪ It's dangerous, I'm falling ♪
♪ There's no escape, I can't wait ♪
♪ I need a hit, baby, give me it ♪
♪ You're dangerous, I'm loving it ♪
♪ Too high, can't come down ♪
♪ Losing my head, spinnin'
'round and 'round ♪
♪ Do you feel me now ♪
♪ With a taste of your
lips, I'm on a ride ♪
♪ You're toxic, I'm slippin' under ♪
♪ With a taste of a poison paradise ♪
♪ I'm addicted to you ♪
♪ Don't you know that you're toxic? ♪
♪ And I love what you do ♪
♪ It's getting late to give you up ♪
♪ I took a sip from my devil's cup ♪
♪ Slowly, it's taking over me ♪
♪ Too high, can't come down ♪
♪ It's in the air and it's all around ♪
♪ Can you feel me now? ♪
♪ With a taste of your
lips, I'm on a ride ♪
♪ You're toxic, I'm slippin' under ♪
♪ With a taste of a poison paradise ♪
♪ I'm addicted to you ♪
♪ Don't you know that you're toxic? ♪
♪ And I love what you do ♪
♪ Taste of your lips, I'm on a ride ♪
♪ You're toxic, I'm slippin' under ♪
♪ With a taste of a poison paradise ♪
♪ I'm addicted to you ♪
♪ Don't you know that you're toxic? ♪
♪ With a taste of your
lips, I'm on a ride ♪
♪ You're toxic, I'm
slippin' under (toxic) ♪
♪ With a taste of a poison paradise ♪
♪ I'm addicted to you ♪
♪ Don't you know that you're toxic? ♪
♪ Intoxicate me now,
with your lovin' now ♪
♪ I think I'm ready now,
I think I'm ready now ♪
♪ Intoxicate me now,
with your lovin' now ♪
♪ I think I'm ready now ♪
- [Airplane Announcement]
Please fasten your seatbelts,
and thank you for flying Toxic Air.
(whoosh)
(birds squawking)